var allQuestions = [

	{
			question : "Which of the following differentiates an antigen from an immunogen?",
			options : ["An antigen is a foreign molecule","An antigen can cause the production of antibodies","An antigen does not always elicit an immune response","Antigens are usually proteins or polysaccharides","Antigens are capable of being bound by immunologic receptors"],	
			correctAnswer : 2
	},
	{
			question : "Which of the following is NOT true regarding effective immunogens?",
			options : ["Foreign to the host","Fairly large (molecular weight > 6000)","Chemically complex (e.g. proteins made of many nucleotide bases)","Requires a carrier-conjugate to cause the generation of antibodies"],	
			correctAnswer : 3
	},
	{
			question : "Which of the following best describes penicillin, a hapten?",
			options : ["Large in size and can induce an immune response alone","Large in size and needs to be coupled to induce an immune response","Small in size and can induce an immune response alone","Small in size and needs to be coupled to induce an immune response"],	
			correctAnswer : 3
	},
	{
			question : "An epitope is generally used to refer to an area on a much larger molecule (e.g., a viral protein) with which an antibody can react.",
			options : ["True","False"],	
			correctAnswer : 0
	},
	{
			question : "Which of the following is NOT true?",
			options : ["The term epitope is not synonymous with antigen","A viral protein may contain a large number of epitopes that are capable of interacting with many different specific antibodies","Immunologic receptors on T cells recognize continuous (linear) epitopes","Immunologic receptors on T cells recognize discontinuous (conformational) epitopes","Antibodies can recognize both continuous and discontinuous epitopes"],	
			correctAnswer : 3
	},
	{
			question : "Which of the following is an agent (e.g. aluminum salts, oil-based, virosomes) oftenused to modify or augment the effects of a vaccine by stimulating the immune system torespond to the vaccine more vigorously, and thus providing increased immunity to a particular disease?",
			options : ["Antigen","Epitope","Immunogen","Stimulant","Adjuvant"],	
			correctAnswer : 4
	},
	{
			question : "What fraction of serum are the antibodies (immunoglobulins) initially found when using lytical techniques (e.g. electrophoresis)?",
			options : ["Albumin","Gamma globulin","Beta globulin","Alpha globulin"],	
			correctAnswer : 1
	},
	
	{
			question : "In the electrophoresis of human serum, which of the following is the most electronegative and thus migrates farthest toward the positive electrode?",
			options : ["Albumin","Gamma globulin","Beta globulin","Alpha globulin"],	
			correctAnswer : 0
	},
	{
			question : "Gamma (!) globulin serum fraction contains predominantly which immunoglobulin?",
			options : ["IgA","IgD","IgE","IgG","IgM"],	
			correctAnswer : 3
	},
	{
			question : "On an early morning run near his home, a runner startled a group of dogs beingexercised and was bitten on the leg. The runner was later unable to locate the dog and itsowner to verify that the dog had an up-to-date rabies vaccination. Given that rabies isalways fatal, and despite the very low incidence in domesticated dogs, prudence dictatedundergoing treatment. The runner was given human immunoglobulin G-containing antibodies to rabies virus (anti-rabies immunoglobulin) injected around the site of thewound and at several other intramuscular sites. This antibody preparation confers instantprotection from the virus without requiring the body to develop a response. This is an example of:",
			options : ["Active immunity","Passive immunity"],	
			correctAnswer : 1
	},
	{	
			question : "The aim of monoclonal antibody production is to produce cells that only secrete immunoglobulin directed against the antigen used in immunization. Which of thefollowing hybridoma production steps is NOT correct?",
			options : ["Immunize a mouse with antigen of choice then remove the spleen when the mouse is making an antibody response","Fuse the immune spleen cells with a myeloma tumor cell","The cells are cultured in a selective medium allowing fused and non-fused cells to survive","Cells are grown in individual culture plate wells, and culture supernatants from wells contains growing hybrid cells are screened for presence of desired antibody by an enzyme-linked immunosorbent assay (ELISA)","This clone (hybridoma) is an immortal producer of the desired monoclonal antibody"],
			correctAnswer : 2
	},
	{		question : "Match the following descriptions with their term: Allows for flexibility",
			options : ["Light chain","Heavy chain","Fab region","Fc region","Hinge region"],
			correctAnswer : 4
	},
	{
			question : "Match the following descriptions with their term: Binds antigen",
			options : ["Light chain","Heavy chain","Fab region","Fc region","Hinge region"],
			correctAnswer : 2
	},
	{		
			question : "Match the following descriptions with their term: Binds to various cellular receptors and to complement",
			options : ["Light chain","Heavy chain","Fab region","Fc region","Hinge region"],
			correctAnswer : 3
	},
	{
			question : "Match the following descriptions with their term: Binds to various cellular receptors and to complement",
			options : ["Light chain","Heavy chain","Fab region","Fc region","Hinge region"],
			correctAnswer : 3
	},
	{
			question : "Match the following descriptions with their term:  Has an fragment crystallizable (Fc) and Fab region",
			options : ["Light chain","Heavy chain","Fab region","Fc region","Hinge region"],
			correctAnswer : 1
	},
	{	
			question : "Match the immunoglobulin(s) with the functional description: Activates the complement system",
			options : ["IgG","IgE","IgM","IgG and IgM","IgG and IgA"],
			correctAnswer : 3
	},
	{
			question : "Match the immunoglobulin(s) with the functional description: Involved in allergic responses",
			options : ["IgG","IgE","IgM","IgG and IgM","IgG and IgA"],
			correctAnswer : 1
	},
	{
			question : "Match the immunoglobulin(s) with the functional description: Predominant in the primary (early) immune response",
			options : ["IgG","IgE","IgM","IgG and IgM","IgG and IgA"],
			correctAnswer : 2
	},
	{	
			question : "Match the immunoglobulin(s) with the functional description: Has different subtypes",
			options : ["IgG","IgE","IgM","IgG and IgM","IgG and IgA"],
			correctAnswer : 4
	},
	{		
			question : "Match the immunoglobulin(s) with the functional description: Can transfer across the placental (maternal protection)",
			options : ["IgG","IgE","IgM","IgG and IgM","IgG and IgA"],
			correctAnswer : 0
	},
	{
			question : "Papain cleaves what region of immunoglobulin?",
			options : ["Heavy chain","Light chain","Hinge region"],
			correctAnswer : 2
	},
	{		question : "Pepsin cleaves what region of immunoglobulin?",
			options : ["Heavy chain","Light chain","Hinge region"],
			correctAnswer : 0
	},
	{
			question : "IgM is structurally characterized as:",
			options : ["Monomeric","Bimeric","Trimeric","Tetrameric","Pentameric"],
			correctAnswer : 4
	},
	{
			question : "Which of the following is the main immunoglobulin in the gut and secretions (saliva, milk, tears) and is important in mucosal immunity?",
			options : ["IgA","IgD","IgE","IgG","IgM"],
			correctAnswer : 0
	},
	{
			question : "Which of the following binds to an Fc receptor on mast cells and basophils?",
			options : ["IgA","IgD","IgE","IgG","IgM"],
			correctAnswer : 2
	},		
	{
			question : "Which of the following is chiefly found on the surface of B cells as a receptor molecule and is involved in cell activation?",
			options : ["IgA","IgD","IgE","IgG","IgM"],
			correctAnswer : 1
	}				

];